

# michalina kamińska

JUNIOR IN IT / PSYCHOLOGIST

## CAREER HISTORY

# Member in association "Woman in Technology"

2020 - present

I'm organizing events connected with IT
 (actually working on webinars about mental hygiene at work, webinars for children "Robocycling" and UX makers online conference).

#### Self-studying / Freelance working 2019 - preser

- A year ago I decided to change my career path because of my personal interest in technology and design. I develop my skills to start working in IT industry.
- I'm studying frontend technologies and UX/UI (using online courses, preparing my own projects to develop my technical skills).
- Now I'm working using Gatsby.js creating website for Academy of Fine Arts in Porto to prepare online exhibition for PhD students.

#### Psychologist 2014 - 2019

Until December 2019 I worked as a psychologist and therapist.
 All my professional experience is related to this position, I cooperated as a small company as well as a dependent person.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **SWPS** in Katowice

Masters in Psychology | Graduated November 2017

**Jagiellonian University in Cracow** 

Masters in Special education, | Graduated July 2013

#### **COURSES / WORKSHOPS**

UX course (March - April 2020)

Organized by: Eduweb.pl

Web developer (September 2019 - now)

Organized by: Altkom Akademia, Katowice (364h)

WordPress&Freelancing course (May-July 2019)

Organized by: CodersTrust Polska

Ruby on Rails workshop (June 2019)

Organized by: Rails Girls Cracow

**Introduction to Java Script (May 2018)** 

Organized by: Girls.js Cracow

HTML, CSS i Java Script (September-October 2018)

Organized by: PLEO method

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am an experienced psychologist and also a beginner in IT world. My professional experience has allowed me to develop cooperation skills as well as understanding group processes. I am motivated and I want to develop my skills in frontend technologies and UX.

I love traveling and exploring different cuisines.

### **GITHUB**

https://github.com/MichalinaKa

#### SOFT AND TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML ★★★☆☆ creative mind with a lot of ideas CSS ★★★☆☆ open JavaScript ★☆☆☆☆ responsibile Gatsby.js + styled components ★☆☆☆☆ adaptable Git ★★☆☆☆ resourceful RWD ★★★☆☆ imaginative Bootstrap ★★★☆☆ versatile AdobeXD ★★★☆☆ pro-active Sass ★★☆☆☆ Jira ★☆☆☆☆

# **CONTACT INFORMATION**

+48 509 353 795 kaminskaa.michalina@gmail.com Al. Korfantego 14/1, Gliwice

#### **HOBBIES / INTRESTS**

yoga | travels | Italian and Asian cuisine web development | UX design illustrations

# **LANGUAGES**

english. ★★☆☆
italian. ★★☆☆
silesian.

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych, innych niż określone w art. 221 §1 kodeksu pracy, zawartych w moim CV i liście motywacyjnym, przez Who Else Poland Sp. z o.o., w celu prowadzenia rekrutacji, w ramach której aplikuję oraz w celu uwzględnienia mojej kandydatury w innych rekrutacjach przeprowadzanych przez wskazany podmiot do końca upływu 2 lat od końca roku kalendarzowego, w którym aplikuję\*. Potwierdzam, że jestem świadoma/y przysługującego mi prawa cofnięcia zgody.